question_data = [

    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }

]
